{
    "subject": "resource/Daphne_Heard",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Plymouth",
    "human_readable": "Daphne Heard was born in Plymouth.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.876232922077179,
            "question": "Name the city where Daphne Heard was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8440356850624084,
            "question": "Where was Daphne Heard born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7354176640510559,
            "question": "In what year was Daphne Heard born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45745980739593506,
            "question": "What is Daphne Heard known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36511901021003723,
            "question": "Where does Daphne Heard currently live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27083316445350647,
            "question": "Is Daphne Heard an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.249578595161438,
            "question": "What are some of Daphne Heard's notable roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19734206795692444,
            "question": "Who are some of Daphne Heard's famous colleagues?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18788328766822815,
            "question": "Has Daphne Heard won any awards for her acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18040388822555542,
            "question": "What type of movies does Daphne Heard typically appear in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Daphne Heard was born in Plymouth.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4729_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Daphne Heard won any awards for her acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4729_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of Daphne Heard's famous colleagues?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4729_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Daphne Heard's notable roles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4729_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4729_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4729_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4729_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4729_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4729_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4729_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4729_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4729_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4729_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4729_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the information provided in multiple documents, which consistently state that Daphne Heard was born in Plymouth, Devon, England."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}